‎总统先生
Mr. President.
‎医生 感谢你能来 请进 ‎我看到你履行了公民义务
Doctor, thank you for coming. Please. I see you did your civic duty.
我投票了
‎你不可以问结果 我如果告诉你的话 ‎可能也有违心理医生职业规则
You can't ask, and it'd probably violate some shrink canon of ethics to tell you,
‎但我不觉得你会不喜欢我的选择
but I don't think you'd be unhappy with my choice.
‎接到我的电话 你意外吗
Were you surprised to get my call?
‎干我们这一行 ‎很快就没那么容易感到意外了
One's capacity for surprise tends to be an early casualty in this line of work.
‎但一位总统候选人这样度过选举日
But it did seem an unusual way for a presidential candidate
‎-确实不寻常 ‎-我不知道
-to spend his election day. -I don't know.
‎1960年 ‎理查德尼克松在南加州投了票
In 1960, Richard Nixon voted in Southern California,
‎跳上一辆白色敞篷车 ‎躲过发布会 去了南边
hopped into a white convertible, ditched the press and headed south.
‎结果来到了提华纳 在那吃了午饭
Ended up in Tijuana, where he had lunch,
‎然后回头跨过边境 漫步向北
then came back across the border, meandered north,
‎一路来到圣胡安卡比斯崔诺教堂
all the way up to the Mission at San Juan Capistrano,
‎走进教堂 找一个空位坐下
entered the church, sat down in one of the empty pews,
‎据说待了好几个小时 再怎么说 ‎我非同寻常的程度也排在他后面
reportedly for hours. So, at best, this would have to rate second.
‎好吧 你想聊什么
Well, what did you want to talk about?
‎我难以入睡
I'm having difficulty sleeping.
‎焦虑性失眠 ‎对总统候选人来说并不陌生
Anxious insomnia can't be unknown to presidential candidates.
‎-这个不一样 ‎-为什么
-This is different. -Why?
‎我要坦白一件事
I have a confession to make.
第三季   第十集
指定
幸存者
擦枪字幕组
XGunSubTeam
精校
发行
mcar.cc
荣誉
出品
合作洽谈     Q:864413459
36小时前
‎该死 加略特 ‎你和菲尔对我做了什么
God damn it, Garrett! What the fuck have you and Phil done to me?
‎你们为什么背着我做这么卑鄙的事
Why would you do this despicable thing behind my back?
科尼利厄斯莫斯
‎你们到底为什么这么做
Why would you do it at all?
‎-嘿 ‎-发现什么了吗
-Hey. -Did you find anything out?
‎你要给律师打电话 我们都要
That you need to call a lawyer. We all do.
复制文件
‎什么事这么重要
What is so important?
‎以此建立律师与委托人间的保密约定
This establishes attorney-client privilege.
‎那只是电视上演的而已
That's just a TV thing.
‎我们要么以老朋友的身份叙旧 ‎要么按我时薪800美元的费率咨询
We can either talk as old friends, or with my $800-an-hour meter running.
‎我感觉你好像需要后者
Seems to me like you might require the latter.
‎我的竞选工作上司 ‎侵入了科尼利厄斯莫斯的手机
My boss on the campaign bugged Cornelius Moss' phone.
‎-你知道多久了 ‎-半个小时
-How long have you known? -Half an hour.
‎-你还告诉谁了 ‎-没有告诉别人
-Who else have you told? -No one.
‎很好 现在拿出手机 ‎打给联邦调查局
Good. Now take out your phone and call the FBI.
‎我猜这部分对话属于要保密的部分了
I'm guessing we've arrived at the privileged part.
‎你担心这会影响柯克曼的获胜机会
You're afraid it'll hurt Kirkman's chances.
‎-他知道吗 ‎-不知道
-Did he know about it? -No.
‎你确定吗 还是只是猜想
You know that or are you guessing?
‎我不确定 但也不是猜想 我了解他
I don't... I don't know that, but I'm not guessing. I know him.
‎拖延下去 ‎你最后可能会帮了他 也可能不会
By delaying, you may or may not be doing him a favor in the end.
‎但我保证 你这样对自己不利
But I can guarantee you're not helping yourself.
‎你拖延不说的每个小时 之后都要
Every hour you don't come forward, you're gonna have to explain that
‎向联邦调查局、联邦检察官 ‎和国会委员会解释
to the FBI, federal prosecutor, congressional committee.
‎代价会很昂贵
It's gonna get expensive.
‎-你会没事的吧 ‎-嗯
-Are you gonna be all right? -Yeah.
‎-有事通知我 ‎-当然 按一小时800块计费
-Keep me posted. -Sure. At eight bills an hour.
‎-你有旧情人优惠 ‎-什么我们从未…
-Well, you get the old flame discount. -What? We were never--
‎我没说不是单相思啊
I didn't say it was requited.
‎我不知道尼克松在那个教堂 ‎想找寻什么 但我不是牧师
I don't know what Nixon was seeking in that chapel,
‎我不提供宽恕
but I'm not a priest. I don't offer absolution.
‎除非你说的是另一种坦白
Unless it's a different sort of confession.
‎你是要讲述一桩犯罪吗
Are you about to reveal the commission of a crime?
‎不是法律意义上的 ‎但可能是道德上的
Not in a legal sense. Arguably, a moral one.
‎但也是需要保密的
Still privileged nonetheless.
‎明白 继续
Understood. Go on.
‎谢谢你 迈克 艾米丽 请坐
Thank you, Mike. Emily, please.
‎怎么了
What's going on?
‎你得听听这个
You need to hear this.
‎该死 加略特 ‎你和菲尔对我做了什么
God damn it, Garrett! What the fuck have you and Phil done to me?
‎你们为什么背着我做这么卑鄙的事
Why would you do this despicable thing behind my back?
‎你们到底为什么这么做
Why would you do it at all?
‎-你从哪弄来的 ‎-根据法律顾问的建议 我不能说
-Where the hell did you get this? -On the advice of counsel, I can't say.
‎-白宫法律顾问吗 ‎-是我的私人律师
-The White House Counsel? -My personal attorney.
‎还有别的事
There's something else.
‎莫斯携带阿兹海默症基因的消息 ‎是我泄露出去的
I was the one that leaked the information about Moss carrying the Alzheimer's gene.
‎什么
Excuse me?
‎我错误地认为我们应该以牙还牙
I wrongly felt that we needed to fight fire with fire,
‎我立刻就后悔了 ‎但是十分羞愧 所以没有告诉你
and I regretted it immediately, but was too ashamed to tell you
‎因为我知道你会对我失望的
because I knew you would be disappointed in me,
‎所以这个录音我必须立即放给你听
which is why I had to play this for you right away.
‎我不能再让你失望一次了
I couldn't fail you again...
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
‎考虑到你极其重视 ‎个人信誉和公平竞争
...and given the high premium that you put on personal integrity and fair play,
‎我知道你会想要纠正错误 不计后果
I knew you'd want to correct the record, consequences be damned.
‎我该走了
I should go.
‎艾米丽
Emily.
‎谢谢你给我这个
Thank you for this.
‎晚安 先生
Good night, sir.
‎你相信录音的真实性吗
Did you believe the sound recording was authentic?
‎-看起来是的 ‎-这不是含糊其辞吗
-Seemingly. -Isn't that equivocating?
‎-我无法确定 ‎-我没问你是否确定
-I couldn't be certain. -I didn't ask if you were certain.
‎我问的是你当时是否相信它是真的
I asked if you believed if it was real.
‎是的 我相信
Yes. Yes, I did.
‎你让我迟到了
You made me late.
‎要怪就怪你自己
You made yourself late.
‎速战速决 ‎又一项因年龄而丢失的能力
The quickie. Another faculty lost to old age.
‎我可没抱怨
-I'm not complaining. -
‎看起来你的候选人要赢了
It appears your boy's gonna win.
‎你父亲没告诉过你 ‎这种话不要大声说出来吗
Didn't your father ever tell you never to say that out loud?
‎他通常以超对手20个点的成绩 ‎赢得再选
He was customarily reelected by a 20-point margin.
‎在我们家 迷信被看作假意谦虚
In our house, superstition was deemed a counterfeit humility.
‎你父亲过去的参议员席位 ‎明年会补选
You know, your dad's old Senate seat is up for special election next year.
‎如果能有对得起 ‎老参议员过去成绩的继任者就好了
It'd be nice to get somebody in there to do justice to the old man's memory.
‎是啊 还能保证柯克曼下个任期议程 ‎有张可靠的参议员选票
Yeah, and be a reliable Senate vote for Kirkman's next term agenda.
‎没那么容易的
It's not gonna be easy.
‎一个没有党派、没有影响力的人 ‎赢得选举 会欠下人情
A presidential win by a man with no party, no coattails, favors owed.
‎这意味着要鞭策普通员工好好工作
Means to whip rank-and-file discipline.
‎-你只需要吓吓他们就好 ‎-是的
-You'll just have to scare them. - Yeah.
‎说到吓人
Speaking of scary,
‎我们收到我的康复费用账单了 ‎真的让我非常难过
we got the bill for my rehab, and I can't help but feel awful about it.
‎-宝贝 你… ‎-更不用说
-Babe, you-- -Not to mention guilty
‎我们能有钱进行治疗的幸运 ‎所带来的罪恶感了
over how lucky we are that we have the means.
‎最重要的是 ‎你已经戒掉了 也决心保持这个状态
The main thing is that you're sober now and committed to staying that way.
‎-再次感谢你这么支持我 ‎-你能回来真是太好了
-Thank you again for being so supportive. -It is so great to have you back.
‎清晨巡逻
Dawn patrol!
‎都过来 这一天来了
Huddle up. Here we are.
‎选举前一天 ‎夜间民调的结果令人振奋
Day before the election. Overnight polling is encouraging.
‎-令人振奋我们赢定了 ‎-别过度自信
Don't get overconfident.
‎在很多战场 ‎我们的优势还在误差范围内
We're still within the margin of error in the battlegrounds,
‎在佛罗里达 ‎中西部北部地区和德克萨斯
in Florida, in the Upper Midwest, in Texas.
‎你听到自己说什么了吗
Did you just hear yourself?
‎“德克萨斯”和“战场” ‎同时出现在一句话里
The words "Texas" and "battlegrounds" in the same sentence?
‎对
Right.
‎你对手一个小小的种族灭绝的阴谋 ‎真的能带来奇迹
It's a wonder what a little genocidal plotting by your opponent will do.
‎但先别这么乐观 你们现在就累了
But let's not count chickens. You think you're tired now?
‎我要你们继续打起十二分精神
I want you next-level spent.
‎我们要去拉票再拉票
We gotta canvass, canvass, canvass.
‎打电话、发推特、出去登门拜访
Work the phones, tweet storms, get out there and knock on doors.
‎我要你们紧追在各州主席的屁股后面
I want you so far up your state chairs' asses
‎烦到他们连打哈欠的时间都没有
that when they yawn, I see your hairline.
‎一起赢下这场选举吧
- Go win an election.
‎大家好运
- -Good luck.
‎艾米丽 等一下好吗
Emily, hang back a minute?
‎我听说你妈的事了 很抱歉 肯定…
I heard about your mom. I'm so sorry. That must have been...
‎天啊 我都无法想象那种感觉
Oh, God, I can't imagine what that was like.
‎如果需要 你今天就休假吧
If you need, just take the day.
‎谢谢 但我没事
Thank you, but I'm fine.
‎-你联系过律师了吗 ‎-你找到飞马座了
-Have you contacted an attorney? -You found Pegasus.
‎我们不能聊这个
We can't have this conversation.
‎-该死 ‎-你今天要陪着总统
-Fuck! -You're with the president today.
‎之后打电话给我
Call me after.
‎-什么之后 ‎-到时候你就知道了
-After what? -You'll know.
‎就算我当时相信录音是真的 ‎也回答不了所有问题
Just because I believed the recording was real, didn't answer everything.
‎如果当时我错了呢如果那是 ‎刻意表演、策略性流出的呢
What if I was wrong? What if it had been staged and strategically released?
‎你是这么怀疑的吗
Is that what you suspected?
‎这是可能的 考虑到当时危急的处境 ‎还有莫斯已经干过的肮脏勾当
It was possible, given what was at stake, the dirty tricks Moss had already played.
‎但那并没有流出到媒体上 ‎而是从你自己的竞选助手那得来的
But it wasn't leaked to the media. It came via your own campaign aide.
‎-所以你所谓的肮脏勾当… ‎-都是胡说
-So, your dirty trick scenario-- -Is bullshit.
‎恭喜你 你问住我了 高兴了
Congratulations, you got me. Happy?
‎你高兴吗你就要当选为总统了
Are you happy? You're about to be elected president.
‎我看起来高兴吗
Do I look happy?
‎稍等
Just a second.
‎进来吧
Come in.
‎嘿 你把这个落在卫生间水池上了
Hey, you left this on the bathroom sink.
‎明天看起来很有希望
Looking promising for tomorrow.
‎是的
Yep.
‎-你还好吗 ‎-不好
-You doing okay? - No.
‎-亚伦的事 ‎-他…
-Aaron? - He was...
‎他和我的父母相处很好 而且…
He was so sweet with my parents, and...
‎他费了很大力气才接纳自己的身份
he's come such a long way in embracing who he is.
‎现在 他就要成为副总统了
And now, he's about to become vice president.
‎而我还是很生气
And I still have so much anger.
‎也许你需要来一场小小的复仇性爱
Maybe you just need a little revenge sex.
‎-没那么好笑吧 ‎-对不起
-It's not that funny. - I'm sorry.
‎整件事情让我变得真的很情绪化
This whole thing just has me really emotional.
‎好吧 是更加情绪化
Fine. More emotional.
‎好消息是
The good news is,
‎这不是必须现在 ‎去想清楚的事 对吧抱歉
it's not something you need to figure out right now, right? - -Sorry.
‎谢谢
Thank you.
‎为什么谈论这件事会让你愤怒
Why does talking about this make you angry?
‎-让我挣扎的是另一件事 ‎-什么
-I was wrestling with something else. -What?
‎我想找到一种叙述的方式 ‎好让它听起来不那么像借口
I'm trying to figure a way to say this without it sounding like an excuse.
‎我不是来评判你的
I'm not sitting here in judgment.
‎这段录音能让莫斯免去多少罪责
How much does this recording exonerate Moss anyway?
‎继续说
Unpack that.
‎从更大的局面看 ‎莫斯和阴谋策划人联合
Moss is in league with the conspirators in a larger sense.
‎从一个人那里拿到大笔钱 ‎再慷慨地用来给另一个人付工资
Accepted huge amounts of money from one, paid a lavish salary to the other.
‎这些人的观点人尽皆知
These men's views were widely known.
‎德特维尔据说曾表示
Detwiler was quoted as saying
‎移民正在让美国成为第三世界国家
immigrants were turning America into a third world country.
‎布朗顿发推说：“我们无法
Brunton tweeted out, "We can't save our civilization
‎在别人的子女身上拯救我们的文明”
on the backs of other people's babies."
‎莫斯非常清楚 ‎自己找来的是什么样的人
Moss knew exactly who he was getting into bed with.
‎如果他选举获胜 他就要为他们负责
And if he wins this election, they're who he'll be accountable to.
‎这样说 你觉得听起来像借口吗
In articulating that, did that sound to you like an excuse?
‎不 听起来像是真相
No, it sounded like the truth.
‎-嘿 怎么样 ‎-你们这些人是虐待狂
-Hey, how's it going? -You people are sadists.
‎在圣安东尼奥、奥斯汀 ‎和达拉斯集会还没到早上9点呢
Rallies in San Antonio, Austin and Dallas? It's barely 9:00.
‎那要吃很多早餐卷饼了
That's a lot of breakfast burritos.
‎-嘿 艾米 你母亲的事我很遗憾 ‎-谢谢关心
Hey, Em, I'm sorry about your mom. Thank you.
‎这里的大家都向你表示哀悼
Everybody here sends their condolences.
‎-你感觉如何 ‎-我没事
-So, how are you holding up? -I'm fine.
‎是吗如果有事 你会说吗
Yeah? Would you say if you weren't?
‎可能不会 那边气氛如何
Probably not. What's the vibe like there?
‎都是对莫斯的厌恶
Oh, it's just disgust for Moss.
‎我还没有完全相信他参与其中了
I'm still not 100% convinced that he was involved.
‎拜托 他的得力助手、最大的资助人
Come on, his right-hand guy, biggest donor,
‎那段手机视频… ‎在德克萨斯 人们肯定都责怪莫斯
that cell phone video... They're sure blaming Moss in Texas.
‎系好你的安全带 今天会很忙
Hmm. Yeah, well, fasten your seat belt. It's gonna be a day.
‎怎么 你知道什么了吗
What, you know something?
‎毕竟选举前一天 事情不会那么顺利
Just, the day before, things go bump.
‎谢谢你打电话来 我要挂了
Thanks for calling. I gotta go.
‎艾米丽 这是我的后代 丝黛芬妮
Emily, this is my offspring, Stephanie.
‎-你好 幸会 ‎-你好
-Hi, it's so nice to meet you. -Hi.
‎非常感谢你给我这个做志愿者的机会
Thank you so much for this opportunity to volunteer.
‎当你在凌晨4点想到这是无偿工作时
Oh, well, at 4:00 a.m., when you remember that you're doing this for free,
‎你的第一个想法可能不是道谢
gratitude may not be your first thought.
‎我带你去见教你工作的人
But let me introduce you to the person who'll show you the ropes.
‎我要发表一个声明 ‎这之后我会接受你们的提问
I have a statement, after which I'll take your questions.
‎莫斯的发布会
Moss presser.
‎我首先要尽全力谴责
I begin by condemning, in the strongest terms possible,
‎这个罪大恶极的生物恐怖袭击阴谋
this unspeakable bioterror plot.
‎我和所有美国人民一起 ‎要求被发现以任何形式参与其中的人
I join all Americans in calling on those found to have played any role
‎受到法律范围内最高限度的惩罚
to be punished to the fullest extent of the law.
‎如果发现要为此事件负责的人
And should it turn out that those responsible
‎包括和我的总统竞选相关者
include persons associated with my presidential campaign,
‎那我欠美国人民一个最诚挚的道歉
then I owe the American people the most profound apology.
‎但是 任何针对我个人
However, any insinuation or outright accusation that I myself
‎参与这场邪恶阴谋 ‎或对其知情的暗示或直接指控
had any role in or any knowledge of this vile conspiracy
‎都完全是无稽之谈
is entirely without basis.
‎因此我也同样要求得到
And I am therefore owed an equally profound apology
‎所有那些 ‎不负责任地下结论的人的道歉
from all of those individuals who have so irresponsibly alleged.
‎尤其是
Most particularly,
‎明天的选举将决出高层办公室的主人
the holder of the high office that is being contested in tomorrow's election.
‎总统先生 我和美国人民
Mr. President, I, and the American people,
‎热切等待着你的道歉声明
eagerly await that statement of apology.
‎听到他这样说 你感觉如何
How did you feel after you heard him say that?
‎我感觉不欠他任何东西
That I owed him absolutely nothing.
‎现在我会回答你们的问题
And now I'll take your questions.
‎-你和总统聊过吗 ‎-聊过
Have you spoken to the president?
‎我表达了我的不满 以及对他的失望
Yes. And I made not only my displeasure, but my disappointment in him known.
‎你是否担心这会影响…
Are you concerned -about the impact that-- -
‎我希望他的监狱室友 ‎是拉丁王帮派成员
I hope he gets a Latin King for a cellmate.
‎阴谋的目的是让德克萨斯这样的州 ‎保持被共和党控制
The conspiracy was about keeping a state like Texas red.
‎现在揭露出来 ‎可能正好会导致他们想避免的情况
And now exposing it may result in exactly what they were hoping to prevent.
‎是的 因果报应 是他们罪有应得
Yeah, karma's not a bitch. She's a freaking queen.
‎请坐
Please, sit down.
‎我在考虑相对于要当副总统的亚伦 ‎你个人的计划
I was wondering about your plans vis-脿-vis Aaron, the vice presidency.
‎这个问题完全是性别歧视 ‎请让我重新说
That's a completely sexist question. Permission to begin again.
‎过去的一年 你的表现让我印象深刻
I've been tremendously impressed with you this past year.
‎我觉得我们合作得很好 非常互补
I think we work well together, complement each other.
‎背景、性别和年龄都是
Background, gender, age.
‎我并不打算离开现在的职位
I have no intention of leaving my position.
‎我不仅仅是不想失去你
This isn't just about not wanting to lose you.
‎如果明天能得到我们想要的好消息
If we get the good news that we expect to get tomorrow,
‎我想让你担任白宫副幕僚长
I'd like to offer you the job of White House Deputy Chief of Staff.
‎我的天
Oh, my God.
‎-你不必现在回答… ‎-好啊
-You don't have to answer right-- -Yes. Yes.
‎当然 我…我很荣幸
Of course. I... I would be honored to accept.
‎好的 我想先说件事
-Okay. Something I want to get a jump on. -
‎富人拥有的康复机构资源
It is manifestly unfair
‎对大部分美国人来说根本支付不起
the kind of rehab facilities available to the affluent
‎这显然是不公平的
that are impossibly out of financial reach to most Americans.
‎你要开始制定策略 ‎想办法迫使大型药企和烟酒公司
Start strategizing on a means to compel Big Pharma, liquor, cigarette companies
‎指定一部分利润用于支付康复费用
to designate a portion of their profits to the cost of rehab.
‎就是说 ‎让他们帮助这些产品的客户脱瘾
Hmm. So help get their customers off the products that they spend so much
‎他们花了太多钱用于营销 ‎引诱这些客户过量使用他们的产品
in marketing dollars enticing them to overuse.
‎我喜欢 你说制定策略是指…
-Mmm-hmm. -I love it. When you say strategize...
‎组建一个跨部门团队
Pull together an inter-agency team.
‎和适合的政府部门联络
Liaise with the appropriate cabinet departments,
‎包括国会的附属委员会
subcommittees on the Hill.
‎你是副幕僚长
You're Deputy Chief of Staff.
‎拿出点架势来好好干
Kick a little ass.
‎我马上去做
I will get right on it.
‎真的吗 迈尔斯 ‎这真是典型的书呆子作风
Really, Myles? This is such a dweeb clich茅.
‎混杂的垃圾 结块的拉面 ‎能让人晕过去的奇多辣椒粉
The thrashed hybrid, the congealed ramen, the faint mist of flaming hot Cheeto dust.
‎好吧 怎么了
Okay, all right. What's up?
‎帮我把我电脑上 ‎所有飞马座的踪迹都抹掉
I need you to wipe any trace of Pegasus off my computer.
‎这一直都在计划中
Yeah, of course. That was always part of the plan.
‎你没听懂我的意思 我要你现在就做
No, you're not hearing me. I want you to do it right now.
‎-这不可能 ‎-什么
-That's not possible. -What?
‎我不能远程操作 ‎我要连接到你的电脑实体才可以
I can't do it remotely, Lorraine. I need physical access to your computer.
‎如果我没搞错 ‎那是在一个玻璃隔间里
Which, correct me if I'm wrong, is in a glass cubicle
‎那个隔间位于接下来36个小时里 ‎华盛顿最繁忙的办公室
in the middle of, what, the busiest office in DC for the next 36 hours?
‎明晚 西部民调结束后
All right, tomorrow night. After the polls close in the west,
‎大家都会去开派对 ‎最后一个人关灯出去后
everyone will leave for the party. As soon as the last man out shuts off the lights,
‎我要你在灯丝冷却前就进去清理干净
I want you in there scrubbing before the filaments cool.
‎-去把你该死的车洗一下 ‎-好
-Get your fucking car washed. -All right.
‎我来问你一个问题 为什么叫我来 ‎如果你对自己的结论已经满意的话
Let me ask you something. Why am I here? If you're at peace with your conclusion.
‎-我对自己的行动不满意 ‎-你说的行动是指…
-I'm not at peace with my action. -By action, do you mean--
‎-指我没有采取行动 ‎-好的 我们来探讨一下
-My inaction. -Okay, let's explore that.
‎柯克曼总统 ‎对前总统莫斯的声明有何评论吗
Does President Kirkman have a comment on the statement by former President Moss?
‎在竞选的最后一天 总统会专注于
On the last day of the campaign, the president is really just focusing
‎对美国人民来说最重要的事
on the issues that are most important to the American people.
‎-赛斯 ‎-赛斯
-Seth? -Seth!
‎莫斯否认自己参与其中 他相信吗
Does he believe in Moss' denial of involvement?
‎总统相信 针对此事的调查
The president believes that the investigation into this matter
‎会深入、全面
will be thorough and conclusive,
‎他认为在调查中 ‎不发表任何额外评论最为合适
and it's most appropriate for him to let it unfold without any additional comment.
‎-赛斯 ‎-柯林
- Seth? -Colin.
‎所以总统坚持认为莫斯参与了阴谋
So the president stands by his statement that he believes Moss was complicit?
‎今天到此为止 谢谢 别忘了投票
That's all I have for today. Thank you, everybody. Don't forget to vote.
‎嘿 ‎在做出这些评论之前 ‎你有没有和总统聊过
Seth, did you speak with the president before making those remarks?
‎有啊 我上台发言之前和他说过话
Yeah, I talked to him before I went up.
‎喂
Hello?
‎我表明莫斯参与了阴谋
I implicated Moss in a conspiracy.
‎现在 我有证据显示他可能是无辜的 ‎却什么也没做
Now, I had evidence that might prove his innocence, and did nothing with it.
‎因为你觉得无论如何 他都有责任
Because you felt he bore responsibility regardless?
‎-是的 我不想让他得到好处 ‎-这话是什么意思
-Yes, and I didn't want to reward him. -In what sense?
‎莫斯不是右翼极端分子
Moss isn't a right-wing extremist.
‎记录显示 他在任时是个温和派
Hell, his record shows he governed as a moderate.
‎-但他变了 ‎-我会说“可笑地转了个身”
-But he changed? -I prefer "cynically pivoted."
‎解释一下
Explain.
‎莫斯想再次当选总统
Moss wanted to become president again.
‎他知道三人竞争时 民主党会偏左
He knew in a three-way race, the Democrats would run to the left.
‎我会保持中立 那他还剩下什么
I'd stay in the center. That left him with what?
‎偏右
The right.
‎所以他把自己 ‎重新塑造成强硬的保守派
So he rebranded himself a hard-line conservative.
‎身边围绕着像德特维尔 ‎和布朗顿这样偏执的狂热分子
Surrounded himself with bigoted zealots like Detwiler and Brunton.
‎他并不认同他们的本土主义理论
He didn't believe in their nativist bullshit.
‎但他知道强硬保守派会投出集体选票
But he knew that the hard-line conservatives would vote in a block.
‎在三方竞争中 这就足够取得胜利了
And in a three-way race, that just might be enough to win.
‎所以你想让他 ‎为自己的不诚实付出代价
So, you wanted him to pay for his dishonesty?
‎-是的 ‎-通过自己的不诚实来实现
Yes. By being dishonest yourself?
‎就像现在的你这样
Like you're being right now.
‎你没有站出来 这样做真的是因为 ‎你不想让他得到好处吗
Not coming forward, was that really because you didn't want to reward him?
‎-不是 ‎-那是为什么
-No. -Why?
‎因为我想赢
Because I wanted to win.
‎他们针对的是你们 休斯顿
They came for you, Houston!
‎不是来杀死你们 ‎他们的计划更隐蔽 可能也更邪恶
And not to kill you. Their plan was more hidden and arguably more evil.
‎他们的目标是你们的未来
They came for your future.
‎他们的目标是 ‎你们永远不会出生的孩子
They came for your children that would never be born,
‎科尼利厄斯莫斯的这些同伴
these associates of Cornelius Moss.
‎他们没料到的是
No, what they didn't reckon with,
‎他们不明白的是 ‎他们的目标不仅是你和我
what they did not understand, is that they didn't just come for you or for me.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
‎而是每一个美国人
They came for every American.
‎他们算计的是 ‎我们的未来、我们的孩子
They came for our future, for our children,
‎是这个伟大、广阔、因多元而骄傲的 ‎美国大家庭的一部分
as part of this great, extended and proudly diverse American family!
‎所以 明天请选择汤姆柯克曼
So tomorrow, elect Tom Kirkman,
‎美利坚合众国所有人民的总统
president of all the people of these United States of America!
‎-嘿 ‎-嘿
-Hey. -Hey.
‎-怎么样 ‎-非常好 其实
-How's it going? -Real good, actually.
‎就连八千次握手带来的 ‎永久性神经损伤仿佛都值得了
Almost worth the permanent nerve damage from shaking 8,000 hands.
‎全世界的免洗洗手液还不够多
Ugh. There's not enough hand sanitizer in the world.
‎-我们会赢的 ‎-德克萨斯吗
-You know, we're gonna win this thing. -Texas, huh?
‎改变局面的一战 谁能想到啊 ‎多亏了汉娜威尔士
Game changer. Who would have thought. Quite the legacy for Hannah Wells.
‎向她致敬
Amen to that.
‎嘿 说来有些尴尬
Hey, this is... This is gonna be awkward.
‎没事 说吧
Yeah, shoot.
‎-伊莎贝尔怎么样 ‎-老兄
-How's Isabel? -Dude.
‎我知道她现在跟你住 ‎你们也互相聊天 对吧
I know she's living with you, and you guys talk, right?
‎-她对我感觉如何 ‎-这是要干什么 我们是中学生吗
-How's she feeling about me? -What is this, middle school?
‎听着 我搞砸了 我知道
Look, I screwed up. And I know that.
‎-但如果这要牺牲我和她的未来… ‎-你爱她
-But if it cost me a future with her-- -You love her.
‎-是的 ‎-那就告诉她 我只能说这么多
-I do. -So tell her. That's all I got.
‎抱歉把你夹在中间
Hey, Seth, I'm sorry to put you in the middle of all this.
‎不是你的错 我也没夹在中间
No, you haven't, and I'm not.
‎-直接跟她说吧 兄弟 ‎-好
-But just talk to her, man, straight up. -Okay.
‎-因为想赢 你没有洗清莫斯的嫌疑 ‎-我刚刚就是这么说的
You didn't clear Moss so you might win.
‎你想解决的问题是 ‎达到这个目的是否可以用这种手段
I just said that. What you're trying to work out is whether the ends justify the means.
‎我认为为了这个国家 当然可以
As far as I'm concerned for the country, absolutely yes.
‎不 对你个人来说 ‎这不就是你想调和的问题吗
No, for you, personally. Isn't that what you're trying to reconcile?
‎“人若赚得全世界 ‎却赔上自己的灵魂 有何益处呢”
"What profits a man who gains the whole world, only to lose his soul?"
‎我觉得我们不需要现在就 ‎派出一支搜救队去寻找你的灵魂
Well, I don't think we need to send out a search party for your soul just yet.
‎你关于莫斯授意为之和不真诚的论据
Your argument about Moss' enabling and inauthenticity,
‎并非浮于表面或不合逻辑
they weren't specious or fallacious.
‎你为什么不解释给美国人民听呢
Why didn't you take them to the American people?
‎一个人很快就会学到 ‎政治不讲原因 更讲情绪
You learn pretty quickly that politics doesn't run on reason, it runs on emotion.
‎人们按直觉投票 ‎再回填论据来支撑自己的选择
People vote their instincts and backfill arguments to fit them.
‎如果我公开那段录音
If I'd released that recording,
‎莫斯本会失去的选民
the voters that Moss would've lost
‎就会有足够的借口恢复心安理得
would have had enough cover to sit on their conscience,
‎无论我说了什么观点
regardless of what point I would have made.
‎谢谢大家 谢谢
Thank you for that. Thank you.
‎感谢你们非凡的投入和不懈的努力
And for your incredible dedication and tireless work
‎刚开始 选举一个独立候选人 ‎成为美国总统
on behalf of what, well, when we started, seemed to be an insurmountable task,
‎看起来还是个难以完成的任务
electing an Independent to the presidency of the United States.
‎而如今 明天我将有机会一战
And the fact that I even have a chance tomorrow
‎这都是这个房间里的人们的功劳
is owed to you, the people here in this room.
‎我将永远心怀感激
And I will be forever grateful.
‎我们已经在过去几个月里
Now, we have put forward over these last few months
‎向美国人民展示了我们最好的一面 ‎现在决定权就在选民手里了
our best case to the American people. But it is now in the voters' hands.
‎为了明天 谢谢你们所有人 谢谢
So, to tomorrow. Thank you all. Thank you.
‎非常感谢 谢谢
Thank you very much. Thank you.
‎你当时感觉会是骗局吗
Did you feel a fraud?
‎当时没有 后来想到了
Not then. That came later.
来电…赛斯
‎-嘿 ‎-嘿
-Hey. -Hey.
‎通知得有点晚 总统邀请我们
Late notice, but the president's invited us,
‎你、我和亚伦 ‎去总统官邸喝东西、吃点心
you, me and Aaron, to the Residence for drinks and dessert,
‎算是呼应你一月刚回来时 ‎我们吃的那顿晚餐
to sort of bookend that dinner we had back in January when you came back.
‎那被他看作是竞选的开端
The one he thinks of as the kickoff to the campaign.
‎你在听吗
You there?
‎是的 我马上来
Uh, yeah. Um... I'm on my way.
‎你准备好在整场国情咨文中 ‎保持僵硬的微笑了吗
You ready to maintain a frozen smile through the entire State of the Union?
‎我打算在他背后比兔子耳朵
I'm planning on doing bunny ears behind his back.
‎只要确保用两根手指就行
-Just make sure you use both fingers. -
‎她来了 你想喝什么
And there she is. What's your pleasure?
‎单一麦芽威士忌 谢谢
A single malt, please.
‎她点的酒比我还有男子气概 ‎这说明了什么
What does it say that her drink is manlier than mine?
‎不言自明了 真的
-Everything, really. -
‎谢谢
Thanks.
‎敬你们所有人 你们在 ‎我相信自己之前 就已经信任了我
To all of you, who believed in me before I was sure I believed in myself.
‎你们帮我回答了 ‎最早艾米丽问的直击要害的问题
And for helping me to answer one of Emily's on-point questions in early days,
‎我为什么要竞选总统
why was I running for president?
‎谢谢你们
Thank you all.
‎干杯 我们阻止了莫斯 ‎和他的优生主义团队
To stopping Moss and his merry band of eugenicists
‎让他们没能把国家改造成 ‎《奥兹和哈里特冒险》
from reshaping the country in the image of Ozzie and Harriet.
‎为您成为人民的总统而干杯
To being the people's president.
‎我以为要像往常一样 ‎敬对政治的远离
I thought it was to be a welcome break from politics as usual,
‎远离勾心斗角和算计
disingenuousness and craven calculation.
‎让正直和诚信重回公众身边
To restore integrity and honesty to the public sphere.
‎-是的 也包括这些 ‎-我为这个干杯
-All right, yeah, all that too. - I'll drink to that.
‎乔 非常感谢
Joe, thank you very much.
‎天啊 只是看看 ‎我都能感觉到血糖在飙升
Oh, man, I can feel my blood sugar spike just from looking at that.
‎女士优先
Ladies first.
‎为什么不呢管它什么良知呢
Why not? Conscience be damned.
‎-谢谢你 总统先生 晚安 ‎-晚安
Thank you, Mr. President. Good night. Good night.
‎-总统先生 ‎-亚伦
-Mr. President. -Aaron.
‎先生 再见
Sir.
‎艾米丽 能留一下吗
Emily, could you stay for a moment, please?
‎当然
Of course.
‎你觉得我欠你一个解释 但并非如此
You think I owe you an explanation. I don't.
‎因为你是总统
Because you're the president.
‎不 因为你在最后关头来找我
No, because you came to me in the 59th minute of the 11th hour
‎拿着一份不能告诉我来源的录音
with a recording, wouldn't tell me where it was from.
‎-那是为了保护你 ‎-据称这份录音
-To protect you. -One that purportedly
‎可以褪去莫斯参与那场阴谋的嫌疑
would have exonerated Moss from having anything to do with this conspiracy.
‎不是据称 是事实
Not purportedly, plainly.
‎我们没有足够的时间来验证其真伪
We didn't have enough time to verify its authenticity.
‎我真不敢相信
I don't believe this.
‎你真的认为我会为了 ‎一段我完全不了解的录音
You honestly think that I would have risked the presidency of the United States
‎赌上美国总统席位的竞选吗
over a recording I knew nothing about?
‎您这样做实在有失尊严 先生 ‎您这是在狡辩 想要…
This is so beneath you, sir. You are self-justifying, grasping--
‎-艾米丽 注意你的措词 ‎-抱歉
-Emily, watch your tone. -I'm sorry.
‎我是不是忘了说“尽管尊重您” ‎要说出这样的话有些困难
Did I not say, "With all due respect"? I'm having a little trouble mustering it.
‎好了 够了 ‎这是我的决定 我已经这样做了
Okay, enough. This was my call to make and I made it.
‎我不需要向你解释什么
I don't owe you an explanation.
‎无所谓 因为我确实没得到解释
Hmm. Just as well, because I certainly didn't get one.
‎祝您明天好运 总统先生
Best of luck tomorrow, Mr. President.
‎-她把信息给你是出于好意 ‎-是的
- Well, she gave it to you good. -Yes, she did.
‎你觉得你值得让她这样做吗
Do you feel like you deserved it?
‎我想这就是我想弄清楚的事
I guess that's what I'm trying to figure out.
‎-又失眠了 ‎-嘿
- Sleepless? Again? -Hey.
‎看起来明天会有好消息 ‎希望这样说出来不会带来反效果
It looks like tomorrow'll bring good news, if it's not jinxing to mention.
‎无论如何 困难的部分已经结束了
The hard part's over, in any event.
‎我知道 竞选并不是困难的部分
I've learned that running isn't the hard part.
‎管理国家会让你这样彻夜失眠吗
Does governing keep you up nights like this?
‎有时会
Sometimes.
‎但也不是工作上的烦恼
But it's not the job, either.
‎那是什么
What, then?
‎不知道自己是否配得上它
Knowing if you're worthy of it.
‎选民们相信你配得上 ‎他们就要推选你连任了
The voters believe you are. They're about to return you to office.
‎明天就会见分晓 ‎最大的问题是 我配得上吗
We'll see. The big question is, do I deserve it?
‎为什么会这么想
Where's that coming from?
‎你要向某人倾诉 ‎哪怕是在祷告里也行
You should unburden yourself to someone, even if just in prayer.
‎试着休息一下
Try to get some rest.
‎-晚安 ‎-晚安
-Night. -Night.
‎-所以你就找到了我 ‎-毕竟上帝不会接我的电话
So, you reached out to me. Well, God wouldn't take my call.
‎嘿
Hey.
‎-我要见总统 五分钟就行 ‎-他留下指示说不接受打扰
-I need five minutes with the president. -He left instructions not to be disturbed.
‎-这对我不适用 ‎-他说知道你会这么说
-That don't apply to me. -He said you'd say that.
‎-如果事关国家紧急情况呢 ‎-是关于国家紧急情况的事吗
-What if this is a national emergency? -Is it a national emergency?
‎你乐在其中 是不是
You're enjoying this, aren't you?
‎有点
A little bit.
‎-谢谢你 拉塞尔 ‎-不客气
-Thank you, Russell. -Don't mention it.
‎志愿者们 统计票数呢
Volunteers, where are my turnout numbers?
‎如果在电视新闻前拿不到数据 ‎你们还对得起零薪水吗
If I can't get them before cable news, what am I not paying you for?
‎-给你 ‎-谢谢
- Here you go. -Thank you.
‎你干得不错 当蒂 我很少夸人的
You have done great work, Dontae. And I'm not promiscuous with my praise.
‎谢谢你这么说
I appreciate you saying.
‎听好 你和艾米丽关系很近吧
Listen, you and Emily are tight, right?
‎她怎么了
What is going on with her?
‎什么意思
What do you mean?
‎-她母亲去世了 ‎-但我觉得还有别的事
-Her mom dying. -But I think there's something else.
‎我一直都跟着总统
I've been on the trail with the president.
‎当蒂 别人会联系我来了解你的
Dontae, people are gonna call me about you.
‎我真的能在职业上帮到你
I can really help you in your career.
‎抱歉 我不知道
Sorry, I got nothing.
‎好吧 谢谢你 当蒂
Well, thank you, Dontae.
‎你是说 你不相信选民
So, what you're saying is, you didn't trust the voters?
‎这让你感觉如何
How does that make you feel?
‎你是一个选民 这让你感觉如何
You're a voter. How does that make you feel?
‎我只负责问问题
I ask the questions.
‎我要为美国人民负责
My responsibility is to the American people.
‎所以是的 我选择不把救生绳索 ‎扔给这个搞种族迫害的骗子
So, yes, I chose not to throw a lifeline to this race-baiting fraud
‎因为我觉得他不适合管理这个国家
because I don't think he's fit to run the country.
‎-在你看来 ‎-在我看来 是的 就是在我看来
-In your view. -In my view. Yes, in my goddamn view!
‎我知道我这样说听起来不民主 ‎但咱们坦白说吧
I know I'm sounding undemocratic here, but let's be honest.
‎这个国家又有多民主呢
How democratic is this country, really?
‎总统选举团、为政党利益改划的选区
With the electoral college, gerrymandered districts.
‎这是不是有点偏离到自我狡辩了
Isn't that straying a little bit into self-justification?
‎是不是可以更简单点 ‎作为总统 你觉得自己懂得更多
Isn't it simpler? That, as president, you just thought you knew better?
‎感谢大家的到来 我长话短说
Thank you all for coming. I won't keep you.
‎我知道你们很多人等着参加胜利派对 ‎或是不愿面对失败后醒来的早晨
I know a lot of you have victory parties to attend and concession wakes to avoid.
‎我请各位国会领导来 ‎是为了讨论未来的方案
I asked you, congressional leadership, here to discuss our way forward.
‎如果投票后的民调数据可靠
If the exit polls are to be believed,
‎那将会是柯克曼大获全胜
it's shaping up to be a resounding Kirkman win.
‎靠的不过是反对另一位 ‎据称涉嫌参与阴谋的候选人的逆反票
A protest vote, against an alleged conspiracy.
‎几乎算不上是授权
Hardly a mandate.
‎意外当选的总统又回来了 ‎依然没有多数党派掌权
The accidental president redux, with still no governing majority.
‎面对现实吧 哈珀 从第一天起 ‎他就是个任期将满的无实权总统
Face facts, Harper. He's a day-one lame duck.
‎这正是我预计会听到的
That's exactly what I expected to hear
‎你们这些德高望重的 ‎华盛顿政圈人士 精明的老手
from you esteemed beltway insiders, canny old pros.
‎说说那个故事吧 别客气
Tell that story, be my guest.
‎讲讲你们那进退两难的僵局
Do your performative gridlock,
‎那悲哀、懒惰的 ‎不为人民办实事的借口
that sorry, lazy excuse for not doing the people's work.
‎我们的故事是这样的
Here's our story,
‎美国选民果断将选举的胜利
that American voters gave a decisive electoral victory
‎交给了一位勇敢的独立候选人
to a fierce Independent to govern,
‎因为他们已经完全受够了你们
because they've had it up to here with all of you.
‎这是对党派僵局的抛弃
That this is a repudiation to partisan stalemate
‎对受私人利益 ‎和美名化贿赂限制的政府的抛弃
and government by self-interest and glorified bribe.
‎我们不仅会把这些信息 ‎传播到所有媒体渠道
And we won't just hammer this message on every media outlet.
‎还要传播到 ‎你们的故乡、所在地区和居住地
We're gonna hammer it in your home states, your districts, where you live.
‎攻击目标就是 ‎你们被说客助长出来的弱点
Blows taking dead aim at your lobbyist-fed, exposed bellies.
‎因为能让这里的人们 ‎有所反应的东西只有恐惧
Because the only thing people respond to in this town is fear.
‎所以记好了 任何从中阻挠的人
So know this. Anyone obstructionist, who doesn't meet us halfway
‎不愿进行善意协商并彼此让步的人 ‎会在初选中遭遇同盟挑战
in good faith negotiation and mutual compromise, will get primaried.
‎既非来自左翼 也非来自右翼
And not from the left or the right,
‎而是来自重要而理智的中间
but from that dead bull's-eye sensible center,
‎也就是多数美国人所在的地方
where the American majority lives.
‎这次选举就好比
This election is the drawing in
‎预示海啸即将到来的退潮
of the waves that foretells the tsunami.
‎所以你们要么好好参与工作
So, either you play ball and play fair,
‎要么就准备好被扫地出门
or be prepared to be swept away.
‎祝你们晚上愉快
Have a good night.
‎-你想从我这得到什么 ‎-你在开玩笑吗
-What is it you're looking for from me? -Are you kidding me?
‎我理解你不是牧师 不能宽赦我
I get that you're not a priest and you can't absolve me,
‎但好歹你要给我点什么
but you gotta give me something, for Christ's sakes.
‎告诉我这种自我厌弃是不对的 ‎是被夸大的 或者至少说 它会过去
Tell me this self-loathing isn't justified or oversized, or at least that it'll pass.
‎你知道这不是由我决定的
You know that's not up to me.
‎病人 你自己疗伤吧 ‎都是你们骗钱的把戏
Patient, heal thyself. Quite a racket you guys got going.
‎我们的时间到了
Our time is past up.
‎至少告诉我 ‎你对你投出的选票后悔了吗
At least tell me this. Do you regret your vote?
‎我只负责提问
I ask the questions.
‎-晚安 先生 ‎-晚安 医生
-Good night, sir. -Good night, Doctor.
‎爸爸 他们打电话来了你赢了
-Dad, they called it! You won. -Oh!
‎-这是你赢得的 ‎-谢谢你 宝贝
-You so deserve this. -Thank you, sweetheart.
‎-我要去准备参加派对了 ‎-好
-I gotta go and get ready for the party. -Okay.
‎妈妈一定会非常骄傲的
Mom would've been really proud.
汤姆柯克曼 再度当选总统
‎这太疯狂了 ‎我拥抱了刚刚认识的人
This is so crazy. I'm hugging people I just met!
‎-恭喜 ‎-谢谢
-Congratulations. -Thank you.
‎你觉得他有能力管理好国家吗
You think he'll be able to govern?
‎会很艰难
It's gonna be an uphill climb,
‎所以弗吉尼亚的 ‎参议员席位一定不能空悬
which is why we can't leave this open Virginia Senate seat up to chance.
‎-你考虑要参选 ‎-不是我 是你
-You're considering a run. -Not me. You.
‎很好笑
Very funny.
‎-马斯 ‎-这是你父亲的旧职位
-Mars. -It's your dad's old seat.
‎没有人比你更了解这里 ‎而你却没有从政经验
There is no one savvier about this town, yet no career politician.
‎而且还有毒瘾 你忘了最重要的事
And a drug addict. You buried the lede.
‎已经戒了 可以就此讲一个 ‎让人动容的故事
Recovered, with a relatable story to tell.
‎你战胜了这个席卷整个州 ‎乃至整个国家的灾祸
A triumph over the scourge plaguing the state and the country.
‎我并不为此感到得意 ‎相反 我觉得如履薄冰
I don't feel very triumphant. More like holding on by my fingernails.
‎那就说说这个 说说每天是如何煎熬
Then talk about that. How it's a struggle every day.
‎柯克曼的胜利让我学到一件事
Look, the one takeaway from this Kirkman win
‎那就是 选民渴望真实
is that the electorate is craving authenticity.
‎你父亲组织过很多高手云集的晚宴
Your father hosted all those glittering dinner parties.
‎你知道他有一次跟我说什么吗
You know what he once said to me?
‎他说你永远是餐桌上最聪明的人
That you were always the smartest one at the table.
‎他从没告诉过我
He never told me that.
‎你也没说过
You neither.
‎因为那些晚宴我也出席了 ‎所以这话也把我比下去了
Well, you know, I was usually also in attendance, so it cut both ways.
‎但他说得对 ‎政治对你来说是与生俱来的
But he was right. Politics is not only in your blood.
‎你这一辈子都耳濡目染
You've steeped in it your whole life.
‎先是在你父亲身边 然后是我身边
First at your dad's side, then mine.
‎你的直观感受 前瞻性的眼光
Your intuitive grasp, seeing around corners,
‎我的整个职业生涯都靠这些了
I have relied on it my entire career.
‎你这样说很贴心
You're very sweet to say all this.
‎我不是刻意说贴心话逗你开心 ‎这关乎我的政治生涯与利益
Sweet has nothing to do with it. It's in my craven political interest.
‎我不知道我能不能做到
I just don't know if I could.
‎我知道
Well, I do.
‎这你得相信我
And you're just gonna have to trust me on it.
‎我不会说考虑一下 ‎因为我会强迫你参选
I'm not gonna say think about it, because I'm gonna make you.
‎每天都在你耳边唠叨 ‎直到递交参选申请截止的那天
Every day until the filing deadline.
‎-我爱你 ‎-我也爱你
-I love you. -I love you, too.
‎-嘿 ‎-现任及未来的总统
Hey. Ah! The once and future president.
‎-这都要归功于你 ‎-不 永远都是候选人的功劳
-I owe this all to you. -No, it's always about the candidate.
‎我的工作就是不要搞砸
In my job, you just try not to fuck it up.
‎我们在这里 ‎一起吃过很多次早餐 一起出谋划策
We spent a lot of breakfasts strategizing here.
‎是的 众所周知的、坦率的意见交换
Yeah, the proverbial frank exchange of ideas.
‎-我让你作出了一些让步 ‎-比我预想的还要多
-I got you to bend a little. -More than I expected.
‎这就是竞选
Such is campaigning.
‎我就不耽误你了 ‎我就是想当面和你说声祝贺
I'll let you go. I just wanted to personally say congratulations.
‎谢谢 罗琳 谢谢你做的一切
Thank you, Lorraine, for everything.
‎总统先生
Oh. Mr. President.
‎进来吧 赛斯 我保证我就快好了
Come in, Seth. I swear I'm almost ready.
‎-嘿 ‎-嘿
-Hey. -Hey.
‎你看上去很美
You look beautiful.
‎谢谢
Thank you.
‎副总统先生
-Mr. Vice President. -
‎感觉如何
How does it feel?
‎德克萨斯州投给我们的时候 ‎我正在鼓励拉丁裔投票的派对上
You know, I was at the Voto Latino party when Texas put us over.
‎亲眼目睹了欢呼雀跃的场景
And just to see the jubilation,
‎那种骄傲和认同感感染着每个人
the sense of pride and that acknowledgment washing over everyone.
‎这对他们来说 对我来说 ‎都意义非凡
And what it meant for them. What it means to me.
‎伊莎 我要为此谢谢你
Isi, I have you to thank for that.
‎还要谢谢那个该死的莫斯
-And that canto de mierda, Moss. -
‎这才是我的伊莎
That's my Isi.
‎这也正是我要说的
Which is my point.
‎你不在那里陪着我 感觉很不好
It just felt wrong that you weren't there with me.
‎我们没在一起是不对的
It's wrong that we're not together.
‎因为我爱你
Because I love you.
‎我知道我不能要求你原谅我
And I know I can't ask you to forgive me.
‎我只是求你再给我一次机会
All I can do is ask that you give me another chance.
‎过去的两天 想着你要当副总统
You know, these last two days, thinking of you as vice president,
‎不知为何我就会热泪盈眶
I'd burst into tears with no idea why.
‎直到现在
Until now.
‎我不能和你在一起 对不起
I can't be with you. I'm sorry.
‎-伊莎 就… ‎-不是因为出轨的事
-Isi, just-- -It's not because of the infidelity.
‎是更深层的原因
It's something deeper,
‎在表象之下 这件事一直困扰着我
something that's always nagged at me under the surface.
‎-你从未认真看待我 ‎-伊莎 你不能这么说…
-You never took me seriously. -Isi, you can't say that--
‎我不是说作为恋爱对象
I don't mean as a romantic partner.
‎我是说作为同事
I mean as a colleague,
‎你从未把我当做一个重要的角色
someone substantial and considerable.
‎现在你做了副总统 情况只会更糟
You making VP now will only make that worse.
‎-你在说什么… ‎-马斯哈珀给我升职了
-What are you-- -Mars Harper just promoted me
‎当他的副幕僚长
to be his Deputy Chief of Staff.
‎-祝贺 那… ‎-看到没就是这个反应
-Congratulations, that's-- -You see that? Right there.
‎你的表情和声音里透露的意外
That surprise on your face and in your voice.
‎这…
It's just...
‎这就能说明问题了 ‎一个不怎么了解我的男人
It's so clarifying that this man who hardly knows me
‎看到了我的一些能力 ‎而我的同居爱人却从未看到
recognizes something in me that my live-in lover never saw.
‎-这不公平 伊莎… ‎-不 你知道什么才是不公平吗
-That's not fair, Is-- -No, you know what's not fair?
‎其实最糟的是
In fact, what really sucks
‎今晚是你人生中最棒的夜晚
is that this is the greatest night of your life,
‎而我却要和你说这些
and I'm telling you this.
‎但你今后的人生不会有我陪伴了
But that life will have to go on without me.
‎-好吧 这个话题我们之后再说… ‎-没有之后了
-Okay, we're not done talking about this-- -We are.
‎结束了
It's over.
‎好吧
All right.  Okay.
‎派对上见
I'll see you at the party.
‎嘿我们做到了
Hey! We did it!
‎是你做到了 ‎我只是个有一点关系的旁观者
Well, you did it. I'm just a not-so-disinterested bystander.
‎天啊 你行使公民权利了
Oh, man, you exercised the franchise.
我投票了
‎还是你为了融入大家 ‎刚刚借来了贴纸
Or did you just borrow that from somebody so you could fit in better?
‎我确实投票了 ‎非常谨慎 但保持乐观
-I actually voted. - Eyes wide open, but hopeful.
‎-在找更重要的人吗 ‎-不
-Looking for someone more important? -No, no, no.
‎-你有伴 ‎-不能算是伴
-You got a date! -Uh, not a date per se.
‎-是你想勾搭的人 ‎-我们算是勾搭过了 生物意义上
-Someone you hope to hook up with? -We kind of already have. Biologically.
‎-她是丝黛芬妮的妈妈 ‎-什么
-It's Stephanie's mom. -What?
‎嘿 你不是该 ‎在保护当选的副总统吗
Hey. Shouldn't you be protecting the vice president-elect?
‎今晚不上班 嘿 恭喜
Off shift tonight. Hey, congrats.
‎这次胜利我完全看作是你的功劳
You know, I'm crediting this entire win to you.
‎可以吗
Is it cool?
‎管它呢 我们赢了
Fuck it. We won.
‎联邦调查局远离那台电脑 ‎联邦探员 李先生
FBI! Step away from the computer! Federal agents, Mr. Lee.
‎我们需要你跟我们走 先生
We need you to accompany us, sir.
‎-你能配合吗 ‎-能
-Will you come cooperatively? -Yes. Yeah.
‎-马斯 ‎-副总统先生
-Mars. -Mr. Vice President-elect.
‎-你认识我妻子的 林 ‎-恭喜
-You know my wife, Lynn. -Congratulations.
‎我太需要感谢你丈夫了
I owe an awful lot to your husband.
‎-没有 ‎-不 他的教导
-No, no, no. -No, no. His mentorship,
‎-指引、言传身教 我… ‎-到时间了 先生
-his guidance, his example. I-- -It's time, sir.
‎没有你 我做不到这些
None of this would've happened for me if it weren't for you.
‎不是的
Not true.
‎那个孩子是个天生的政治家
That boy is a born politician.
‎他是个明星
He is a star.
‎所以我想让他 ‎为你的参议员竞选做巡回演说
Which is why you want him stumping for you on your Senate run.
‎-艾米丽 ‎-嘿
-Emily. -Hey.
‎-为你的母亲表示哀悼 ‎-谢谢
-Condolences about your mother. -Thank you.
‎-你是不是不得不帮她… ‎-是的
-Is it true you had to be the one to... -Yeah.
‎-你一定感觉很糟 ‎-多谢关心
-How awful for you. -I appreciate that.
‎我想跟你道个歉
I wanted to apologize over
‎为之前因为亚伦的事对你的态度
how I acted towards you with the whole Aaron thing.
‎-我完全理解 ‎-不
-Totally understandable. -No.
‎不 怒气应该全撒在
No, it's fucked up to blame the woman
‎出轨的男人身上 女性不该受责备
when all of the anger should be directed towards the cheating guy.
‎我刚和他彻底分手了
Who I just ended it with for good.
‎-不是因为… ‎-不是
-Not because of-- -No. Uh...
‎和那没关系
No, nothing to do with that.
‎-有空我们应该一起吃个午饭 ‎-可以啊
-We should grab lunch sometime. -That'd be nice.
‎我感觉不太好
I'm not feeling well.
‎如果有人问起 ‎你能告诉他们我回家了吗
Could you just let people know I went home? I mean, if anyone asks?
‎-行 你好好休息 ‎-谢谢
-Yeah. Feel better. -Thanks.
‎我们刚刚得到消息
And we're getting word right now.
‎前总统莫斯正在竞选中心发表演讲
Former president Moss, taking the podium at his campaign headquarters.
‎谢谢
- Thank you. Thank you.
‎我刚打电话给柯克曼总统 ‎祝贺他竞选成功…
I just called President Kirkman to congratulate him on his victory...
‎祝他和这个国家前途似锦
...and to wish him and the country all the best going forward.
‎但考虑到导致我今晚需要
But I would be remiss for not noting the circumstances
‎发表败选演说的现状 我不敢怠慢
that led to needing to give a concession speech this night.
‎荣誉感和公平竞争意识遭受侵蚀
The erosion of a sense of honor and fair play
‎是这导致了我们现在的局面
that has brought us to this moment.
‎在以后的日子里 我会就这一点
I will have more to say on this and other matters
‎和其他事项发表更多言论
in the days and weeks and months ahead.
‎因为今晚 我可以打包票
Because tonight, I can say with assurance
‎未来一段时间 你们一定会看到
that you most definitely will have Cornelius Moss to kick around
‎科尼利厄斯莫斯发表言论
for some time to come.
‎谢谢大家 愿上帝保佑美利坚合众国
Thank you all, and may God bless the United States of America.
‎嘿 我是迈尔斯 ‎我正躲着不接你的电话
Hey, it's Myles, and this is me ducking your call.
‎留个言 或者不留也行
Leave a message or don't.
‎谢谢
Thank you.
‎我非常骄傲和高兴地
It is with great pride and pleasure
‎向大家介绍现任和下一任美国总统
that I introduce to you our current and future president
‎汤姆柯克曼
of the United States, Tom Kirkman!
‎上来吧
Come on.
‎感谢你们所做的一切 我马上回来
Thank you for everything. I'll be right back.
‎谢谢 非常感谢
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you very much.
‎对于大家在我参选时给予的巨大支持 ‎我表示受宠若惊和荣幸之至
I am deeply humbled and honored by the incredible support my candidacy has received
‎感谢你们今晚来和我一起庆祝
from those celebrating with me here tonight,
‎也感谢全国各地成千上万的人
to the tens of millions across this great land
‎他们信任我、为我送上 ‎这个国家最宝贵的物品
who've entrusted me with the most precious commodity
‎也就是他们的选票
this great nation has to offer, their vote.
‎现在轮到我 ‎在接下来的四年里向大家证明
It now falls upon me to prove to you over the next four years
‎你们对我的信任是正确的
that your faith in me was justified.
‎对于还没能信任我的人们
Now, for those who couldn't muster that faith,
‎对于将这场胜利看作失败的人们…
for whom this victory feels like defeat,
怀孕
‎…我保证同样会为你们努力工作
I pledge to work equally hard for you,
‎倾听你们的诉求 尊重我们的不同
to listen to you, to honor our differences,
‎但永远带着谦卑与尊重 ‎去了解相反的观点
but always engage opposing ideas -in a spirit of humility and respect. -
‎因为我们正是 ‎通过表达差异让自己成长
For it is through the airing of our differences that we grow
‎个人如此 国家也如此
as individuals and as a country.
‎接纳差异不仅让我们成为更好的人
Acceptance of those differences doesn't just make us a better people,
‎这也是作为美国人最重要的品质
it is the essence of what it means to be an American.
‎今天我不是独自取得胜利 ‎很多人都做出了贡献
Now, I did not get here alone. Many people contributed to this victory.
‎-罗琳齐默 ‎-是的
-Lorraine Zimmer? -Yeah?
‎联邦调查局 请跟我来
-FBI. Come with me, please. -
‎但没有这个人 我完成不了这一切…
But the person I could not have done this without...
‎好吧
Yeah, okay.
‎…从一开始就站在我身边
...standing beside me right from the start,
‎新任副总统 我的朋友亚伦萧
is your new vice president and my friend, Aaron Shore.
‎我知道你靠不住 但没想到你这么蠢
I knew you were treacherous. I didn't take you for this stupid.
‎你刚刚污染了 ‎总统选举历史上最伟大的胜利
You've just tainted the greatest victory in presidential history.
‎-女士 ‎-看看你
- Look at you,
‎站在道德制高点上
high on the fumes of your moral superiority.
‎你是个因为自己心情不好
You're the one who fucked someone else's man
‎就跟别人的男人上床的人
because one day you felt sad.
‎你泄露了莫斯的基因检测结果
You're the one who leaked Moss' gene results
‎因为你以为没人注意到
because you thought no one was looking.
‎我还听说 你都没能 ‎妥当地杀死你可怜的妈妈
Hell, the way I heard it, you couldn't even kill your poor mama right.
‎-你这个该死的禽兽 ‎-我知道自己是什么样的人
-You're a fucking monster. -I know what I am.
‎我是获得胜利的人 你他妈算什么
I'm someone who wins. What the fuck are you?
‎-我们该走了 女士 ‎-我还想要
- I would also like to take a moment
‎特别感谢艾米丽罗德
and add a particular thanks to Emily Rhodes,
‎她从最开始就陪伴着我
who's been with me from the very beginning.
‎她见过我最好的状态 ‎当然也见过我最糟的状态
She has seen me at my best, and most assuredly, my worst.
‎她的水准与高度是我一直努力的方向
And whose highest of high standards I will always endeavor to meet.
‎我开始竞选时谈到过 ‎我们的政治感觉崩坏了
Now, I began our campaign noting that our politics felt broken.
‎他们说竞选总统 ‎就像对自己的灵魂拍X光片
They say a presidential campaign is like an X-ray into your soul.
‎（园景体育馆）
Our institutions diminished.
‎机构缩减 谈话粗糙
-Our discourse coarsened. -
‎就让今晚成为纠正一切的第一步
Let tonight be the first step in setting all that right.
‎这是我做的事吗 ‎还是说现在我就是这样的人
Is this just something I did? Or is this who I am now?
‎让我们共同努力 让辩论恢复文明
Let us come together, restoring civility to our debates,
‎让治理重回透明
transparency to our governance!
‎下次我演讲时
Next time I give a speech,
‎我的脑中会不会有个声音悄悄说…
will there be some corner of my mind just whispering...
‎最重要的是 ‎让诚信重回美国人民身边
And above all, honesty with the American people!
‎…“全都是胡说八道”
..."You are so full of shit"?
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手
对字幕有任何意见和建议的同学请加Q群：544487177